{
    "subject": "resource/Giovanni_Battista_Piranesi",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1778",
    "human_readable": "Giovanni Battista Piranesi died in 1778.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9244043231010437,
            "question": "When did Giovanni Battista Piranesi die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6997237801551819,
            "question": "In what century did Giovanni Battista Piranesi live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6817528009414673,
            "question": "Where is Giovanni Battista Piranesi from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6588388681411743,
            "question": "What is known about Giovanni Battista Piranesi's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6453986763954163,
            "question": "What was the profession of Giovanni Battista Piranesi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6444641351699829,
            "question": "Was Giovanni Battista Piranesi an artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6209673285484314,
            "question": "Who were some contemporaries of Giovanni Battista Piranesi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46855512261390686,
            "question": "Are there any famous works by Giovanni Battista Piranesi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43016234040260315,
            "question": "How did Giovanni Battista Piranesi influence art history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40689945220947266,
            "question": "What kind of art did Giovanni Battista Piranesi create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giovanni Battista Piranesi died in 1778.",
            "html": "dbpedia_955_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Giovanni Battista Piranesi influence art history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_955_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous works by Giovanni Battista Piranesi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_955_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some contemporaries of Giovanni Battista Piranesi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_955_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_955_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe query is asking if Giovanni Battista Piranesi died in 1778. According to the context information, all four documents confirm that Piranesi was born on October 4, 1720 and died on November 9, 1778. This information supports the triple, so the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Giovanni Battista Piranesi died on November 9th, 1778, in Rome."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}